[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
I don't know if you've seen it they have
like a lot of these social media ads yes
foreign speakers
[Music]
foreign
it'll be easier now
be sure
[Music]
wait for babies
okay that's what we usually get right
vibrant critical illness
[Music]
if you're excited
um
foreign
if you were to build a financially
stronger Philippines what Innovations
would you love to have
yeah
apple juice
investment
interesting interesting insurance
one less problems
[Music]
information
and think of the right answer
do you think you have an advantage
[Music]
hello
[Applause]
John Cena
um
[Music]
Innovations
live streaming
uh
foreign
[Applause]
City party